Long ago, in ancient China,
在很久以前 在古r候的中
the Peacocks ruled over the Gongmen city.
孔雀一族y治著mT城
They brought great joy and prosperity to the city,
因火的l明
for they had invented fireworks.
他y治下的P凰城一片g废楹偷木跋
But their son, Lord Shen,
但是他的鹤 沈王
saw darker path in the fireworks.
lF了火黑暗的一面
What that brought color and joy,
那就是它不H可以砩彩和g愉
could also brink darkness and destruction.
也同涌梢砗诎岛
Shen's troubled parents consulted to Soothsayer.
沈的父母o奈之下求助於A言家羊M姑
She foretold that if Shen continued down to this dark path,
她告]孔雀夫D如果沈^m研究火的黑暗面
he will be defeated by a warrior of black and white.
有一天他被一黑白勇士打
The Young Lord set out to change his fate.
年p的沈妄D改自己的命\
But what he did next, only sealed it.
但是他之後所做的 s印C了A言
Shen returned to his parents full of pride.
沈志得意M地回到父母身
But in their faces, he saw only horror.
s只乃的上看到了@恐
He was banished from the city forever.
他被永h地逐出了mT城
But Shen swore revenge.
但是沈l誓他蟪鸬
Some day, he will return,
有一天 他回
and all of China would bow at his feet.
到r 整中原都⒊挤於他_下
It's almost done, Lord Shen. But we ran out of metal.
就快完成了 沈王 但是我的金儆猛炅
Search the furthest villages, find more metal.
搜ぷ钸h的村落 掘地三尺也得找砀多金
China will be mine.
中原就快是我的了
And then the Dragon warrior joined the Furious five.
然後神大b加入了w世五b
So they became the most awesome Kung Fu team ever.
於是他M成了史上最的功夫M合
Enough talk. Let's fight.
f得蚨嗔 我_打吧
Listen, listen! You can hear the Dragon warrior training right now.
快 快啊! 神大b正在Y面呢
Thirty-three, stop him. It's too dangerous.
三十三 行了 e^m了 太危U了
Thirty-five.
三十五了
- Stay focus.  - Thirty-six.
- 集中精力  - 三十六了
Thirty-seven.
三十七了
How is he doing that to his face?
他的怎N可以@N扭曲?
Thirty-eight bean buns.
三十八豆沙包
Yes. New record. You monster.
新o了 你@怪物
- Keep going, hit forty.  - He never hit forty.
- ^m啊 n羲氖  - 他]有^四十
You got it, buddy. I'm going to forty!
你f得 夥 我要挑鹚氖!
- Do it.  - No problem.
- 塞M去  - ]}
Wait a moment.
等等
- He did it.  - Well done Po.
- 他成功了  - 值煤 阿
Your training is paid off.
你的要t到了
Oh, Master Shifu. Gotta go. See you later.
哦 父在等我 我得走了 一阂
You'll save those to me, right?
你o我留些包子的 是吧?
Inner peace.
平o
Oh. Inner peace.
哦 我的心如止水啊
Master Shifu.
父
Master Shifu. What do we got? Pirates?
父 怎N了? 有海I?
Vandals of volcano mountain?
火山上淼耐暨_人(古日耳曼人的一支 似於中古代的U族)?
Whatever it is I will take them down. Cuz I'm in the mood.
不管是l我都打∷的 因槲椰F在SS欲
I need to get something done, you know what I mean?
我得找人修理一D 你到了?
What are you doing?
你在质颤N啊?
One of Master Oogways' final teachings.
觚大留下的一最K教x
Awesome. How did you do that?
太棒了 您怎N做到的啊?
- Inner peace.  - Inner peace. That's cool!
- 刃牡钠届o  - 刃牡钠届o 太酷了!
- Inner peace of what?  - It's the next phase of your training.
- 什N是刃钠届o啊?  - @就是你下一A段要修的热
Every master must find his path to inner peace.
每位宗都必自己找到刃钠届o的方法
Some chose to meditate for 50 years in a cave just like this.
有些人x裨诙囱ㄑY像@于は胛迨年
Without the slightest taste of food or water.
B最基本的食物和水都不需要
- Or?  - Some find it through pain and suffering as I did.
- e的呢?  - 有些人通^v痛苦磉_到 像我就是
Po, the day you were chosen as Dragon Warrior,
阿 你被x樯颀大b的那天
was the worst day of my life.
就是我人生中最K淡的一天
By far, nothing else came close.
到目前橹 ]有什N比得上那天了
- It was the world's most painful, mind destroying, horrible moment,  - Okay.
- 再也]有比那r候更痛苦 更o助 更摧意志  - 好了
I have ever experienced.
的v了
But once I realized the problem was not you, but within me,
但是後砦野lF }不在你 而是在我自己身上
I found inner peace, and was able to harness the flow of the universe.
我_到了刃钠届o的境界 能蜃匀绲伛{S宇宙的川流不息
So that's it. I just need inner peace?
所以f 我只需要_到刃牡钠届o就可以了?
My inner is already super-super peaceful.
我@Y面已超超平o了
So all I need to do is just get this thing going.
所以我只需要@泳托辛
Inner peace. You're going down.
刃钠届o 你快掉下砹父
Now show me what you were doing there with your feet. I saw you just sort of a fancy...
我看看你怎N用_支蔚 在我看碚媸遣豢伤甲h...
Po!
阿!
Bandits, approaching the musicians' village.
狼群悍匪正在u村
Danger. Tell those musicians to start playing some action music because it is on.
好U啊 告V那些演奏些痈械囊 因槲要_打了
Don't worry Shifu, I will master inner peace, as soon as I get back.
父 你e心 我一回砭透你W刃钠届o
No snack stops this time.
@次可]有ng零食rg了
Ha-ha-ha! Snack stops.
哈哈哈! ng零食
Wait, are you serious?
等等 你f真的?
Get all the metal you can find.
把所有能找到的金俣ё
Grab the metal.
快去金
Help, help, help.
救命啊 救命啊 救命啊
That's everything. Let's get out of here.
都拿到了 我走吧
Wings of justice.
正x之翼砹
The Dragon Warrior.
神大b
Panda? That's impossible.
熊? 不可能吧
My fist hungers for justice.
我的拳^渴望著正x
That was my... fist.
@... 好吧 就是拳^
Get them.
抓住他
Come on.
戆
Take that.
@招
Po, incoming.
阿 小心
Thanks, Mantis.
xx 快螳螂
Tigress, double-jump strike.
悍苫 我p合璧吧
Feet of fury!
佛山o影_!
Tigress.
悍苫
Monkey. Viper.
猴王 俏小
Mantis. Bunny. What?
快螳螂 小白兔 什N?
Oh sorry.
哦 Σ黄
- Crane, go.  - I'm on it.
- `Q 快去救人  - 我砹
Is everyone OK?
大家都好吧?
Awesome!
太棒了!
I got this.
我Ω端
Shoo on that, Toby!
享受吧 死胖子!
- Are you okay?  - What happened?
- 你]事吧?  - 怎N了?
I think I saw.
我好像看了
I think...
看了...
I gotta go.
我得走了
Thank you for coming to Dragon Warrior Noodles and Tofu.
g迎光R神大bI食豆腐店
More tea? Lemon sauce? If you need anything, just ask.
需要茶? 是檬u? 有什N需要管_口
Thank you.
xx
Dragon Warrior's mop. He might be very poor.
神大b的甙 他那r候肯定很F
No touching, you'll get the mop dirty.
e碰 弄v的
- He was waiting on me.  - Awesome.
- 他r在等我  - 太爽了
I have a stand to prove it. Hey. Where is the Dragon Warrior?
我就是碚宜C明的 嘿 神大b在哪?
He does not work here anymore.
他不在@Y工作了
He's busy out there. Protecting the valley.
他F在很忙 得保o整子
- The Dragon Warrior.  - Po.
- 神大b  - 阿
Here, OK.
碛HH 好
You should have told me you were coming.
你碇前先告V我一下啊
Hi dad.
嗨 老爸
- I would save you some stinky tofu.  - Ah.
- 我o你留一些臭豆腐的  - 呃
- Ah, can I talk to you?  - Of course, son.
- 老爸我能跟你f事?  - 然了 鹤
In honor of my son: Free tofu desserts for everybody...
榱擞接我鹤: 我所有人吃豆腐c心
with purchases.
然X是得付的
So good to see you. Po.
看到你真高d 阿
Have you lost weight?
你瘦了?
I could almost put my wings around you.
我都快能抱你了
Maybe a little.
可能是瘦了c
Po, you must feel weak. Let me get you some soup.
阿 你肯定很I吧 我斫o你做
That's OK dad. I'm not hungry.
xx 老爸 但是我不I
Not hungry? Po you alright?
不I? 阿你怎N了?
Yeah, I'm fine, I just.
嗯 我]事 我只是
Earlier today, I was fighting with the bandits. Nothing too dangerous.
今天早些r候 我正和狼匪打Y 然]什N危U
They were just... you know.
他很水的... 你知道
And then, the strangest thing happened.
然後 突然l生了奇怪的事情
I had a crazy vision.
我好像出F了幻X
I think I saw my mom, and me as a baby.
我好像看了自己小r候和我在一起的幼
Mom? A Baby?
你? 小r候?
Dad?
老爸?
What he talk about?
天 他f什N?
How do I say this?
我怎Nf呢?
Where did I come from?
我哪淼?
Well you see, son.
鹤 你看是@拥
Baby geese come from a little egg.
小Z是涅Z蛋Y孵出淼
Don't ask me where the egg comes from.
e我蛋哪淼
Dad, it is not what I meant.
老爸 我不是@意思
I know it's not.
我知道你不是@意思
I think it is time to tell you something,
是r候告V你些事情了
I should have told you a long time ago.
一些早就告V你的事
You might have been kind of,
你其是我
adopted.
收B的
- I knew it.  - You knew? Who told you?
- 我就知道  - 你怎N知道的? l告V你的?
No one. I mean, come on dad.
]有人告V我 我是f 得了老爸
But if you knew it, why didn't you ever say anything?
但是你要是早就知道 槭颤N你聿我呢?
Why didn't you say anything?
你也]f^啊?
How did I get here dad? Where did I come from?
老爸 我怎N磉@旱? 我哪淼?
Actually,
其
you came from this.
你是倪@Y出淼
It was just another day at the restaurant.
那是一晴朗的午後
Time to make the noodles.
我在I^Y_始渥雒
I went out to the back,
我去屋後面拿
where my vegetables had just been delivered.
送^淼男迈r蔬菜
There were cabbages, turnips, radishes...
有孕牟 菁 小}N...
Only there were no radishes.
但是 小}N都]了
Just a very hungry baby panda.
取而代之的是一|I的熊
There was no note.
F]有任何留言的l
Of course you could have eaten it.
然也有可能是被你吃了
I waited for someone to come looking for you.
我想等等看有]有人碚夷
But no one did.
但是]人出F
I brought you inside,
我把你Щ匚葑友Y
fed you,
o你吃的
gave you a bath,
湍阆丛
and fed you again,
再o你j吃的
and again.
一直喂
I tried to put some pants on you.
我想o你穿l子
And then I made a decision that would change my life forever.
然後我做了一改我一生的Q定
To make my soup without radishes,
就算我以後的Y都]有小}N了
and to raise you as my own son.
我也要把你H鹤眇B
Sao Po. My little panda.
小阿 我的小熊
And from that moment on, both my soup and my life,
哪且葬 我的和我的人生
have been that much sweeter.
都得更加甜蜜了
My little Po. That's the end of the story.
我的小阿啊 故事就到@了
Look at me. No, do not look at me.
看著我 算了 e看我
That's it?
就@些?
That can't be it. There's gotta be more, dad.
不Π 有些故事的
Well, there was the time you ate all of my bamboo furniture.
好吧 有些P於你吃光我所有竹u砭愕氖虑
It was important too.
也挺值得一f的
One dumpling please, Dragon Warrior size.
我要一神大b吃的那N大包子
Oh Po, your story may not have such a happy beginning,
哦 阿 你的故事或S]有一快返拈_始
but look how it turn out,
但是看看F在
you got me, you got Kung Fu, and you got noodles.
你有我 有功夫 而且你有神大b牌Il
I know, I just have so many questions.
我知道 我只是有些疑
Like how did I ever fit in this tiny basket.
比如 我怎N能bM@N小的箱子的
Why didn't I like pants.
槭颤N我不喜g穿子
And who am I?
有 我到底是l?
Good, Watch your thought.
好 跟著感X走
Good.
好的
Shen?
沈?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
下午好 各位
Now we've got the pleasantries out of the way.
客套咱就不f了
Please leave my house.
你x_我的地P
Your house?
你的地P?
Yes, didn't you see the peacock on the front door?
然了 你]看T上的孔雀苏I?
There you are, Soothsayer.
你好啊 羊M姑
It seems your fortune and skills are not as good as you thought.
貌似你的A言水平和\舛]有想像的那N好啊
We shall see, Shen.
我走著瞧 沈
You shall see, old goat, where were we?
你明白的 老砘 哦我f到哪毫?
- What do you want Shen?  - What is rightfully mine...
- 沈 你到底想质颤N?  - 我要Z回本砭凫段业...
Gongmen city.
mT城
Gongmen is under stewardship of the master council.
mT城F在由L老管理
And we will protect it.
我保lmT城不受外人侵犯
Even from you.
即使是你也不例外
I'm so glad you feel that way.
我很高d你@N想
Otherwise they drag that gift for nothing.
不然他拖著@Y物就白忙一隽
What's in the box, Shen?
沈 箱子Y的是什N?
Want to see it? It's a gift.
你想知道? 是Y物
It is your parting gift.
@是用矸纸饽愕亩Y物
It will part you.
它把你肢解
Part of you here, part of you there,
把你炸得@阂K 那阂K
and part of you where you were there...
有一K就在你F在站的地方...
staining the wall.
你血R
You insolent fool.
你傲慢的蠢
- Show off.  - That is a warning.
-  不e嘛  - @只是警告
You are no match for our Kung Fu.
比功夫 你根本就不是我的κ
I agree, but this is.
我知道 但它是
Are you familiar with the master of Gongmen city?
你知不知道mT城的城主?
- Master thundering Rhino?  - Yes.
- 雷霆犀牛大b?  -  就是他
- Son of the legendary Flying Rhino?  - Yes.
- 髡f中翔天犀牛b的鹤?  -
And the slayer of ten thousands serpents in the valley of Wolf?
在豪枪韧绞执狄匀f的巨蛇的那?
- He's dead.  - That, that is impossible.
- 他死了  - @ @不可能啊
Rhino's horn defense is impervious to any technique.
犀牛b的F布衫不是金不
There were no techniques. Lord Shen has created a weapon.
他不是§段湫g 沈王造了一新武器
One that breathes fire and spits metal.
一吞火吐的武器
Unless he is stopped. This could be the end of Kung Fu.
如果不阻止他 @是功夫的末日了
But I just got Kung Fu.
我才W功夫啊
And now you must save it.
所以你F在必拯救它
Go! Destroy this weapon,
去吧! 摧那武器
and bring Lord Shen to justice.
⑸蛲K之以法
OK here we go.
好的 我出l吧
Wait a second, how can I do this?
等等 我怎N做得到呢?
I mean how Kung Fu stop something that stop Kung Fu.
我是f功夫怎N去阻止一要KY功夫的|西呢
Remember Dragon Warrior, anything is possible,
神大b 住 你心如止水的r候
when you have inner peace.
你o所不能
Inner Peace.
刃牡钠届o
Peace on.
平o了
Po. I get you travel bag.
阿 我o你把行囊都收拾好了
I pack you food for week, cookies,
我替你打包了一星期的食物 乾
buns, vegetables, and even pack all your action figures. See!
小I包 蔬菜 上了你所有的玩具人偶 瞧!
Oh! Er... Hey, I don't know what those are.
噢! 呃... 嘿 我不知道那是什N
Never seen them before in my life.
之前焊就]^
Dad, you make a scratch on my Tigress.
爸 你了我的苫⑼媾
I also pack your painting, the best time together,
我替你放了些 P於一起度^的快r光
just in case you get lonely.
只是以防f一你孤
That me and you making noodles,
@的是我和你在做Il
and that me and you eating noodles.
@是我和你在吃Il
And that me giving you a piggy back ride.
@ 是我你T著玩
That cute, on second thought, I'll hang on to this one.
真可 我再想想要不要o你看看@
Hey, they are waiting for me.
嘿 他在等我呢
Of course, of course, you have a job to do. Far from home.
然 然 你有事要去做 hx家l
A strange city, filled with strange people and strange noodles.
去陌生的城市 到都是陌生人和陌生的Il
Facing horrible danger, from which you might never return!
面可怕的危U f不定因此永h回不!
Don¡¯t go, Po.
e去 阿
I got to go, I'm Dragon Warrior,
我得走了 我是神大b啊
It's kind of my job to save kungfu.
拯救功夫是我的使命
And if I don't. What am I?
如果我不去 那我是什N?
You are my son.
你是我鹤
Right?
不是?
Po, it's time.
阿 走了
Goodbye.
再
Don't worry, Mr. Ping, He will be back before you can say "noodles".
e心 平先生 在你能f出"Il"@~之前 他就回淼
Noodles.
Il
Come on guys, let's go.
快c 夥 我走
Mom? Dad? Is that you? Mom! Dad!
? 爸爸? 是你? ! 爸爸!
Oh hi, hey hey, son, you are back.
哦嗨 嘿 嘿 鹤 你回砹
Honey, what are you doing here?
你在@Y质颤N?
- But I thought...  - We replaced you, dear, with a lovely radish.
- 可我以...  - H鄣 我用你Q了一可鄣奶}N
Radish?
}N?
He is quiet, polite, and frankly does better kungfu.
他又安o 又Y貌 而且f 功夫比你好
Wait.
等等
Radish, radish, ra...
}N }N }...
Inner peace.
刃牡钠届o
Pea...
平...
I'm, er, training.
我 呃 正在
The mast is not a worthy opponent.
桅U可不是好κ
I'm ready.
我浜昧
Ok. So serious.
好吧 @N烂C
I think I prefer the mast.
我想我是打桅U比^好
Apologize, I used to punch iron wood tree by the paws in training.
抱歉 我以前的r候常常徒手打F
Now I feel nothing
所以F在我什N也感X不到
That is severely cool.
那太酷了
Again.
再
So this punching iron wood tree,
那N 打F溥@事
how long did you have to do that?
你之前了多久?
- Twenty years.  - Oh twenty, twenty years.
- 二十年  - 哦 二十 二十年
Is there any faster way? You know until don't feel anything.
有什N更快的方法? 就是 得什N也感X不到
No. Besides...
]有 另外...
I don't think hard style is your thing.
我不J 勤W苦m合你
Po. Why do you really out here?
阿 你槭颤N要跑到外面?
I just found out my dad isn't really my dad.
我只是lF我爸不是H生的爸爸
Your father? The Goose.
你爸爸? 那只Z
That must have been quite a shock.
@δ憧隙ù舨恍
Yeah.
是啊
And this bothers you?
@件事你很困_?
Are you kidding me? We are warriors, right?
你在_玩笑? 我是大b 不是?
Nerves of steel, souls of Platinum. Like you.
有F般的神 真y般的意志 就像你
So hardcore, you don't feel anything.
F石心c得什N也感X不到
- I was...  - So what are you talking about?
- 我曾...  - 你在聊什N呢?
Nothing.
]什N
Po is having daddy issue.
阿正在mY他老爸的}
I'm so lucky, I don't have any problem with my dad.
我真幸\ 我爸爸]出^}
Because my mother ate his head before I was born. I don't know.
因槲在我出生前就把他X袋咬掉了 我什N也不知道
Mantis, it is not about you, Po is the one freaking out.
螳螂 不是在f你 阿┑枚伎彀l了
I'm not freaking out.
我才]有l呢
Po.
阿
I'm freaking in.
我在ld
- Po!  - what?
- 阿!  - 什N?
We are here, Gongmen city.
我到了 mT城
My father's throne.
我父H的王位
He always let me play here beside him.
他以前常我在旁玩
Promising someday this throne would be mine.
SZ我 有一天@王位是我的
A little to the left.
往左一c
But it is so heavy, Master.
可是它太重了 大人
Thirty years, I've waited for this moment.
我等了三十年 就檫@一刻
Everything must be exactly how I've envisioned.
一切都必按我O想的
And I envisioned,  a little to the left.
而我O想的就是 往左一c
Perfect.
完美
With the weapon, by my .. left a bit more.
{借@件武器 就在我... 再往左一c
With the weapon, by my side, all china will be bowed for me
{借@件在我身的武器 整中原都⒏┦茁命
We move out in 3 days,
我⒃谌天後出l
when the moon is full and the tide is high.
趁著月M潮q
Now you old goat, why don't you tell me my...
F在 你@老山羊 槭颤N不向我ff我的...
Fortune?
命\?
The future, I was going to say the future.
未 我要f的是未
Looking to your bowl,
看著你的碗
And tell me what glorious waits
告V我 前方有的是怎拥妮x煌
If you continue on your current path ...
若你仍猿盅巯碌牡缆...
You will find yourself...
你lF自己...
At the bottom of the stairs.
走下了@台A
I see...
我看...
I see pain
我看了痛苦
and anger
和怒
How dare you, that is the finest suit in the province.
好大的子! @可是全省最好的一件衣服
followed by denial.
以及否J
This is not fortune telling. You just say what is happening right...
@哪Y叫A言 你f的事情就l生在...
Now?
F在?
The most important time is now.
最重要的r刻就是F在
But if you really want to see the future...
不^如果你真的想看看未...
What do you see?
你看到了什N?
A peacock...
一b孔雀...
Is defeated by a warrior of black and white.
被一黑c白的大b打×
Nothing has changed.
什N都]
That's impossible. And you know it.
那不可能 你知道的
It is not impossible. And he knows it.
@K不是不可能的 他也知道
Who?
l?
- Lord Shen. I saw a pandas.  - A panda?
- 沈王 我看了一b熊  - 一b熊?
A kungfu warrior, he fought like a demon.
一功夫大b 他就像耗б痿Y
Big and fury, soft and squashy.
身形汛T 填膺 毛皮柔又皲
Kind of plushy and cuddly.
毛茸茸的又可
There are no more pandas.
世界上已]有熊了
Even with the poor eye sight, he can see the truth.
就算他眼神再不好 也能看真相
Why is that you cannot?
槭颤N你看不呢?
Find this panda and bring him to me.
找到@只熊 Щ斫o我
Yes, sir.
是 先生
One panda lives, that does not make you right.
有只熊活著 但@不代表你就是Φ
You are right, being right makes me right.
你f得 事才C明我是Φ
Then I will kill him and make you wrong.
那我就把他⒘ @幽憔褪清e的了
Would you stop that!
你能不能消停!
That must be Shen's palace in the other side of the city.
城的另一^一定就是沈王的m殿
Great, we march to the tower and proclaim...
棒O了 那我就直奔那座高塔 然後宣...
we are the Dragon Warrior and Furious Five
我是神大b和w世五b
and we are here to bring you justice.
我淼竭@Y 要⒛憷K之於法
What are you doing?
你质颤N?
This place is crawling with wolves.
@Y全DM了狼
Hey, isn't that the guy who hammered you in the face.
瞧 那不是n你的砸了一N的砘
I do not like that guy ...
我一c阂膊幌g他...
We need to get to that town without being spotted by those wolves.
我得悄悄M城 不那些狼lF
Got it. Stealth Mode.
t解 行模式
Ow...
哎呦...
Hello. Hehehehe, I ...
你好丫 呵呵呵呵 我...
OK. anyway, Where was I?
好了 管他呢 我才走到哪了?
- Where is Po?  - How can we lose a guy that big?
- 阿在哪Y?  - 我怎N弄G@N大K^?
Guys, guys?
人呢 人呢?
- Po...  - Sorry.
- 阿...  - 哦 Σ黄
So that was stealth mode huh?
那N @就是行模式了 哈?
Be honest, not one of my stronger mode.
老f @可不是我的
You got more gold. Come on.
你有更多的金子呢 拿出
This rice is raw.
@米是生的
You stole of my metal pots for Lord Shen.
可你把我的F偷去o沈王了
- Either you cook my rice or I cook you.  - My pot is...
- 要N把我的煮好 要N我把你煮了  - 可我的...
Po, do something.
阿 想想k法
How am I supposed to help the cook-rice without getting caught?
我要怎N做才能退煮完不被捉?
Wait. I have a better idea.
等等 我有好主意
- One...  - Hey? Hey?
- 一...  - 嘿? 嘿?
We are here to liberate the city and bring Shen to justice.
我是斫夥胚@座城市 K⑸蛲K之以法的
You will need help.
你需要椭
Thank you, brave sheep. But it was too dangerous and I can't let you...
xx 你是只勇敢的羊 可是@太危U了 我不能你...
- Oh, not me. It's not safe to speak here.  - Right.
哦 我不是f自己 @Yf不安全  - ]e
I'm talking about Master Ox and Croc.
我f的是牛大b和{大b
They are in Gongmen jail, at Black Dragon area.
他被P在mT城的牢房 就在黑^
What? They are still alive?
什N? 他活著?
They must be in that jail to gathering intelligent hatching
他一定在牢Y收集情 密\策著
a plot to use their awesomeness to defeat the weapon.
如何用他的@世才能打∧俏淦
OK, let's go. Thank sheep.
好吧 我走 xx你 小羊
Hey! Stop that costume!
嘿! r住那舞的!
Get them.
捉住他
Uhh... Sorry!
呃... 抱歉!
Take... That!
LL... @!
Keep going! Faster!
接著跑! 快c!
Now.
F在
Got you...
捉到你了...
Huh?
什N?
Where did they go?
他去哪毫?
Spread out!
大家散_!
Search everywhere!
搜遍所有地方!
What about over there?
那阂搜?
Is "there" a part of every where?
"那"是所有地方的一部分?
I... I guess.
我... 我猜是的
Then search there!
那就去搜!
They must be close.
他就在附近
I can feel a Kung Fu chill riding up my spine!
我能感到一功夫的寒意Z上我脊背
Sorry, Po. It's just me!
Σ黄 阿 才是我!
Look!
瞧!
Gongmen Jail!
mT城Oz!
Oh... It's cute.
哦... 真可
Cute? Huh?
可? 嗯?
Nice work, Po.
值煤 阿
At the first sight of trouble, I'll give you a signal.
只要一看苗^不 我就提醒你
Gaga... Gygy!
嘎嘎... \\!
- You mean like Crane does?  - Yeah!
- 你是f 像`Q那咏?  - ]e!
Excuse me, when have I ever, made that noise?
隈{ 我什Nr候 l出^@N噪音了?
Master Ox! Master...
牛大b! 牛...
The ferocious Master Croc!
流星{大b!
Hey... Master storming Ox!
嘿... 暴LF牛大b!
I can't believe, we're rescuing actual legends of Kung Fu.
我直不敢相信 我正在I救活生生的髌婀Ψ蛉宋
We will free you from those bondages, just no problem, gotta be a key around here.
我把你救出 ]}的 @附近肯定有匙
No, they wouldn't leave a key around here.
不 他不可能把匙留在@
Oh, good... You found it! Come on you guys. Yeah!
喔 很好... 你找到匙了! 戆纱筲 耶!
We're coming for you, Shen!
我碚夷闼阗~了 沈王!
Guys, are we going or not?
夥 我是走是不走啊?
Do we need to do this later?
要t一些邮?
I mean, you do wanna take back you city. Right?
我是f 你_想Z回@座城吧 是?
Of course, we do.
我然想
But if we stand up to Shen,
但如果我和沈王作
he will turn the weapon on the city!
他就把炮口D向整座城!
Listen to yourself.
你在f什N
You're protecting Gongmen city, by not protecting Gongmen city?
你保omT城的方法 就是不保o它?
If we all fight together...
如果我K肩作...
Then the weapon would kill, everyone.
接著那武器就⒌ 所有人
Oh, would it?
哦 ?
Then we use... A sneak attack!
那我就裼... 偷u!
- We'll get inside, and then...  - And then you'll be stopped!
- 我偷偷入 然後...  - 然後你就被r住!
By the unstoppable weapon.
被那o法阻止的武器打
when I'm stopping you from telling me something unstoppable.
]有什N是o法阻止的!
Master Ox, I'm not let you stay in the cell!
牛大b 我不你待在@牢房Y的!
I like to see you get me out!
我倒要看看你怎N把我弄出去!
You guys see that? It's called being awesome!
大夥嚎匆了? 那叫一牛!
Come on! whatever happened being hero?
拜 回英雄又怎N了?
The only hero in this town, is a dead one.
@城市Y唯一的英雄 已死了
Like I said, you are not getting me out of the cell!
如我所f 你]法把我睦窝Y弄出去!
Yes!
行了!
Alright. Let's go!
好吧 我走!
I get the top bunk.
我要睡上
It's time to surrender, panda.
是r候放了 熊
Kung Fu is dead!
功夫已死了!
I...
我...
You... You... Kung Fu is a dea..aa.ad!
你... 你... 功夫已死...死...死了!
Fine!
好吧!
You stay in your prison of fear!
你就待在你那恐值男±畏垦Y吧!
With bars made of hopelessness.
被^望的Fli住
And all you get is 3 square meals a day of... shame.
你唯一有的只是一日三餐 被羞u填得的
With despair for dessert.
有^望的甜c
We'll take on Shen.
我去和沈王^一高下
And prove to all those who hunger for justice!
向所有那些渴求正x和s耀的人C明!
And honor, 'The Kung Fu still lives'.
"功夫依然存在"
Yeah!
耶!
Monkey!
猴王!
Gaga!
嘎嘎!
You... You're mine!
你... 你是我的!
I'll tell you what's gonna be yours.
我告V你 你有的是什N
My fist in your plush cuddly super soft face.
是我那只n你毛q可圮趴趴的打^淼娜^
Uh-ouh!
啊哦!
Get him!
捉住他!
- Get me out of here!  - Yes, sir!
- 我出去!  - 是 先生!
- Stop him!  - Yeah!
- r住他!  - 耶!
Faster!
再快c!
Po, go!
阿 快追!
- Lose him!  -Yes, Sir!
- 甩掉他!  - 遵命!
Hang on!
抓o了!
Watch out!
心啦!
Very uncool!
太不地道了!
Try this!
LL@!
Guys, guys, guys.
大伙 大伙
Maybe something small.
要不睃c小砘
Oh, no!
噢 e!
You better get off my face!
你最好快c奈夷上爬下!
Pardon me! Ok, pardon me.
不好意思! 不好意思
Fire! Fire!
火哦! 著火了!
We lost them.
我跟G了
Yeah! Again!
好哎! 再硪淮!
Crane, catch!
`Q 接著!
Guys, guys, guys... give me a shot!
夥 夥... 助我一臂之力!
Mantis, now!
快螳螂 乘F在!
Is that all you got to defeat us?
你就@c本事想打∥?
This cloud is about to bring the thunder!
暴L雨在後^呢!
Your turn!
到你了!
Why there are... so... many... signs?
槭颤N@Y有... @N... 多... 招牌?
Come here!
o我^!
I like to squash you.
我就喜g核滥
Yes! Taste of the defeat.
好的! L到失〉奈兜懒税
Let me tell you something...
我告V你...
Next time you mess with a panda, you better bring a whole...
下次惹熊的r候 你最好上全套的...
Guess nobody told you, if you mess with a wolf...
大概]人告V你 如果你招惹狼的...
You'll get the fangs.
你只被狼咬
I hit you twice...
我打了你纱...
What are you gonna do now?
你奈我何?
We surrender!
我投降!
You could chain my body but you will never chain my... warrior spirit.
你能i住我的肉w 但是你o法i住我... 武b的精神
- Hey, don't forget the little guy!  - Did you just called me...
- 嘿 e忘了@小砘!  - 你叫我...
Po, what're you doing?
阿 你在做什N?
Trust me, I gotta a... pla... ww!
相信我 我心中... 有... 哇!
No way!
不吧!
Eight-point acupuncture cuffs!
八B拷!
Just like the one that held Tai Lung, the more you move the tighter they get...
就像拷住泰狼的那 你越暝它s的越o...
These are "the" best cuffs.
的_是"最"好的手D
Greetings, panda. At last we meet.
好啊 熊 我K於面了
No. No, no, no..
不行 不行 不行...
We meet at last!
我K於面啦!
Yes! That's it!
很好! 就它了!
Greetings, panda. We meet at..
好啊 熊 我K於...
You are afraid for a reason.
你的害怕不o道理
I'm not afraid.
我才]有害怕
He's coming to me in chains.
他可是еD硪我的
Have anyone should be afraid? It's...
如果有人害怕的? 那是...
You!
你!
Don't you even think about it.
你想都e想
I hope this turns out better than your plan to...
我希望@次Y果比你上次想出的
cook rice in your stomach by eating it raw and then drinking boiling water.
把生米和沸水灌M肚子Y碇箫的要好
This plan's nothing like that plan.
@可不像上次那一
How?
怎Nv?
Cuz is one's gonna work!
因檫@成功的!
Keep moving.
e停下
Ah... My old enemy!
啊... 老κ掷!
Stairs!
又是翘!
Thanks for carrying me. This is last free flight.
多x你背我 可@是最後一次免M旅程了
Okay. I threw up a little bit on the third floor,
好吧 三堑r候 我吐了一下下
Someone might wanna clean that up.
也S有人去清理一下
There's some sort of evil janitor, or something?
是不是派什N邪菏匦l 是什N?
Greetings, panda. We meet at...
好啊 熊 我K於...
Hey, how you doing?
嘿 你好?
Hey...
嘿...
You've grown up bigger than I thought.
你的K^比我想像中要大很多啊
Hey, okay. Enough of... the poking around.
嘿 好吧 看... 了
Healthy.
健康
Look, I don't know who you are. But please stand aside, sir.
著 我不JR你 你站到一去 先生
That's a lady!
那是女士!
Oh... sorry!
哦... 不好意思啊!
The beard threw me, it's kind of misleading.
@E子我搞混了 有c`О
False avatar.
形象不Π
Enough of this nonsense!
Uf完了]!
Bring the prisoners to me.
把犯人o我上
Sorry ma'am. Get ready guys, keep your eyes peeled for the..
不好意思啊 女士 大伙眼睛擦亮c 看清楚...
Weapon!
武器!
Sparrow kick!
旋踢!
We did it! I just Kung-Fued it. Did you guys see that?
我做到了! 我用功夫打碎了它 你都看到了?
I was all like...
我就好像是...
Waao!
哇_!
Do you actually believe this is the warrior destined to defeat me?
你真的相信@就是命中注定打∥业挠率?
I do not!
我不是相信!
I know he is.
我知道他的
Look at him!
你看看他!
A lifetime to plot his revenge, and he comes me on his knees.
花了一子rg聿统鹩 而他就跪在我的面前
What? A life time... Wo-wo-wo! I did not have a life time.
什N? 一子... 喔! 我可]用一子的rg
We only heard about master Rhino a few days ago,
我滋烨安怕f雷霆犀利大b的消息
And we've came to avenge him!
我硎樗蟪鸬!
You've come to avenge, nothing else?
你砭褪榱蟪鸬 ]有其他事了?
Well, Yeah. All the pots and pants that you stole,
然有啦 所有你偷的那些碗瓢盆
I want those back.
我都要回
Nothing else?
有呢?
You probably did some evil stuffs along the way.
你一路上可能做些什N氖
I don't know. What else did you do?
我不知道 你做^其他什N事?
- You don't know?  - Know what?
- 你不知道?  - 知道什N?
What's so funny?
有什N好笑的?
Many things.
好笑的事情多了
Did you clearly do not know?
你真的什N也不知道?
Okay, enough for these riddles!
好了 ≈i蚨嗔!
Would you guys spill the beans?
你就不能oc暗示?
First we know, we came in and the weapon is tiny.
起先 我走了M 那武器很小
Surprise, it's big.
突然的 它就大了
And then, lady over here, I think is a guy, he's got...
然後 那的女士 我反正X得是男的 他有...
The only reason you're still alive,
你活著的唯一原因
is that I find your stupidity, mildly amusing.
是因槲野lF你很蠢 略Ц阈
Well, thank you. But I found your evilness, extremely annoying!
多xF 但我lF你很 特e的┤!
Who do you think you are, panda?
你以槟闶钦l啊 你熊?
Who do you think am I, peacock?
你X得我是l啊 你孔雀?
Why are we laughing?
我槭颤N要笑啊?
Take him.
值羲
Fire!
_火!
Well, light that thing.
哎 c火啊
I did!
我c了!
Here the bug!
我硪!
Get the weapon!
去武器!
Tigress!
悍苫!
- You... you were there.  - Yes. Yes, I was!
- 你... 你r在  - ]e 我的_在!
You just let Shen get away.
你把沈放跑了
At least, we destroyed the weapon.
至少 我把武器oЯ
Fire!
_火!
Uh... No! He's got a way more.
哇... e啊! 他有很多存
Wow!
喔!
My wings!
我的翅膀!
- Help, Po!  - Coming!
- 兔 阿!  - 砹!
Watch out!
心!
Po!
阿!
- Help me up!  - No. Get him down.
- 把我拉上去!  - 不用 放他下去
Use the ropes.
用那些K子
Run, run. Little panda!
逃吧 逃吧 小熊!
Come on! We need you to focus.
拜! 我需要你集中注意力
I've got it, I've got it!
我知道 我知道!
Bring 'em down!
值羲!
- We trapped!  - This way.
- 我被困住了!  - 走@Y
Good bye!
再啦!
Fire!
放箭!
Get back!
退回去!
The only way out is up.
唯一的出路就是往上
What?
什N?
Follow me.
跟我
Come on!
快c!
Where are they going?
他去哪Y?
To the top!
去!
Come on, keep going!
快c e落下!
Here we go!
我砹!
You idiot!
你蠢!
My nose!
我的鼻子!
Call in the wolves.. All of them!
召集狼群... 所有人!
I want them ready to move!
我要他溟_船!
The year of the peacock, begins now!
孔雀元年 就此_始!
Right now?
F在?
'Cause it's the middle of the year.
因榻衲瓴胚^了一半
So you only get, like a half of the year of peacock.
所以你就剩下 一半的孔雀元年
Get the wolves ready.
狼群浜
We're loading the ships, now.
我F在就b船
Now!
F在!
Now, now, now...!
F在! 就F在...!
Move, move, move!
快走 快走!
This way.
@Y
Go!
走吧!
Oh... you!
哦... 是你!
What did you do?
你都至诵┦颤N?
It's chaos up there. What happened to stopping Shen?
上面y成一粥了 你榱俗柚股蚨甲隽诵┦颤N?
Yeah.
的好
Guys, come on! Give me a little credit.
夥 拜! ξ矣悬c信心
I met for him, to get away,
我著了他 他逃了
'Cause.. it's a trick, it was a plot!
因... 那是陷阱 是\!
I was thinking, uh, figure out his plot... more.
我想著 嗯 λ的\... t解的更多一c
That makes no sense.
@]道理啊
What you mean? It sure does.
你什N意思? 很有道理啊
Po, the truth! You had Shen.
阿 真相呢! 你明明抓住沈了
What happened?
l生了什N事?
What're you talking about? I don't know, what are you talking about?
你在f什N? 我不知道 你在f些什N?
Uh.. Yeah! Ahh.. He caught me off guard.
哦... 是的! 呃... 我放警惕了
The truth!
真相呢!
Fine!
好吧!
They'll keep you far from danger.
他保o你不受害的
Real far.
^Φ
What?
什N?
You're staying here.
你就呆在@Y
Wa... wait!
等... 等一下!
I have to go back.
你必要回去
You are staying here.
你就o我呆在@Y
I'm going ,and you can't stop me!
我要去 你阻止不了我!
Okay, I wasn't ready that time.
不算 我才]浜
Guys, don't!
你z e@!
Ready!
浜昧!
Look!
看那!
Stay down.
e逞了
I have to get to him.
我必要抓到他
Then tell me why!
那就告V我槭颤N!
He was there, okay?
他r在那 行了吧?
The Peacock was there, the last time I saw my parents.
我最後一次看到我父母的r候 那孔雀就在那
He knows what happened.
他知道l生了什N
Where I came from.
我哪难Y
Who I am.
有 我是l
Look, I'm going.
著 我要去
I have to know.
我必要知道
The hardcore can't understand.
你@F人是不懂的
Tigress! No!
悍苫! 不要!
The hardcore do understand.
我懂
But I can't watch my friend be killed.
但是我不看著我朋友去送死
We're going!
我出l!
Hey, maybe you can't watch me being killed.
嘿 或S你不看著我去送死
Stop being a wimp.
e懦夫
And she's back.
她又回砹
Don't worry kid. You're better off here.
e想太多 呆在@Y挺好
You're wrong, Soothsayer.
你的A言是e的
We sail to victory tonight.
我R上就能起航了
Your magic panda is clearly a fool.
你所^的勇士就是傻瓜
Are you certain the panda who is the fool?
你{什Nf 那只熊是傻瓜?
You just destroyed your ancestors' home, Shen.
你Я四愕墓示 沈王
A trivial sacrifice.
oPo要的奚
When all of China is my reward.
到r候中原整都是我的
When will you be finally satisfied?
那r候你就M足了?
Will the subjugation of the whole world
只有征服全世界
finally make you feel better?
才能你感X好?
It's a start.
@只是_始
I might as well convert the basement into a dungeon.
我把地下室改造成地牢
The cup you choose to fill has no bottom.
@可是o底洞啊
It is time to stop this madness.
是r候停止@N狂的行榱
Why on earth would I do that?
我{什N要@N做?
So that your parents can rest in peace.
@幽愀改覆拍馨蚕
My parents hated me.
我父母我
Do you understand?
你懂?
They wronged me.
他e怪了我
And... I will make it right.
而且... 我要m正@一切
They loved you.
他勰
They loved you so much that having to send you away, killed them.
他是那N的勰 所以把你送走他心痛欲^
The dead exist in the past.
^去已o法改
And I must turn to the future.
我必要直面未
Set the soothsayer free.
放了羊M姑
She's no use to me.
她ξ乙呀]有用了
Goodbye, Shen.
再了 沈王
I wish you happiness.
希望你能得到快
Happiness, must be taken!
我的快 已被Z走了!
And I will take mine.
而我要重新Z回
Hurry it up!
e磨蹭!
If all of those weapons leave the building,
如果那些武器全部\出去
China will fall.
中原必S陷
We bring down the building.
那我就摧н@座建B
Hey guys.
嘿 夥
How about this?
@怎N
Oh!
噢!
This will work.
@能行
Alright, let's go.
好 行影
I can't feel my face.
我的]知X了
Dumb hell crow... year of the Peacock.
死的蠢B... f神R孔雀年
Hey.
嘿
Keep it cool, keep it cool.
淡定 淡定
You!
你z!
Where are you going?
往哪走呢?
On your feet!
站起!
And wipe those stupid grins off your faces.
e他嬉皮笑的
Move, you dogs! Faster! Faster!
悠 你 快c! 快c!
Load them all!
把它全部b上船!
Greetings, Panda.
你好啊 熊
Tell me what happened that night?
告V我那晚l生了什N
What night?
哪天晚上?
That night!
就是那一晚!
Oh, that night.
哦 你f那天晚上啊
Yes!
]e!
We are talking about the same night right?
我f的是同一晚上吧?
Yes, I was there.
是的 那晚我在
Yes, I watched your parents abandoned you. It was a terrible thing.
]e 我H眼看你的父母了你 太可怕了
I believe it went something like this!
就像@!
Here's your new year's gift!
送你的新年Y物!
Hope you like it. Cause you can't return it.
希望你能蛳g噢 不喜g也不退噢 H
Po?
阿?
What is he doing here?
他磉@致?
Return it! Return it!
退! 退!
Are you willing to die to find out the truth?
莫非你真的是死也要知道真相?
You bet I am!
那然!
Although I prefer not to.
管我是不想死
We got them! Go!
我砀愣ㄋ! 你快去!
Looking for me?
在找我呢?
I said that too soon, didn't I?
我是不是f的太早了?
Po!
阿!
Po, get away from him.
阿 甩掉他
No more running, Shen!
你跑不掉了 沈!
So it seems.
看起硎前
Now, answers.
f吧 F在
Oh, you want to know so badly.
哦 你@N急著知道啊
You think knowing will heal you, uh?
看砟阏J檎嫦嗫梢园涯阒伟K?
Fill some craters in your soul.
a你心`所受的的
Well, here's your answer.
好 你o我好了
Your parents didn't love you.
你的父母根本就不勰
But here...
但F在...
let me... heal you.
就我... 斫o你好好治治
No..ooo!
不要!
Huh!... Ohhh!
哼!... 哎呦!
Ya, like you can make me drink that.
切 b得就像你能逼我喝下那玩意核频
Argh...arghh...
( ⊙ o ⊙ )啊...
If I wanted you dead,
我要是想你死
I would have left you in that river.
就不把你暮友Y救上
Why did you save me?
你樯毒任?
So you can fulfill your destiny.
榱俗你完成你的使命
What are you talking about?
你在f什N啊
Where am I?
我@是在哪啊?
What is this place?
@是什N地方?
I'm surprised you remember so little.
我真]想到你啥都不得了
But you were so little when it happened.
不^那r你_很小
Perhaps you do remember.
也S你是得的
Remember what? It's just a stupid nightmare.
得喊 那就是愚蠢的噩舳已
Nightmare? Or memory?
噩? 是?
This was a thriving village.
@涸是欣欣向s的村f
Young Shen was in line to rule Gongmen City.
年p的沈本陶mT城
But he wanted more.
但是他想要的可不止@些
I foretold that someone would stand in his way.
我A到了有人碜柚顾
A panda.
是一b熊
But I never could have foretold what came next.
可是我o法A接下l生什N
Get them all.
把他全部值
Take our son and run away! Go!
上我的鹤与x_@! 快走!
Stop fighting. Let it flow.
不要暝 要其自然
Your story may not have such a happy beginning.
也S你的故事]有一快返拈_^
But that does not make you who you are.
但那Q定不了你是l
It is the rest of your story.
重要的是在接下淼墓适卵Y
Who you choose to be.
你想要成檎l
So, who are you, panda?
那N 你是l 熊
I am Po.
我是阿
And I am gonna need a hat.
我需要一帽子
Such sad-sad faces.
瞧@一幅幅可z影
But now is a time only for joy.
不^F在到了_心的r刻了
You are going to be a part of something beautiful.
你成橐美景的一部分
Once you reach the harbour, in front of all the world.
你到了港口 在所有人面前
You and your precious Kung Fu will die.
你和你的功夫一同缤
Then China will know to bow before me.
接著整中原便向我俯首Q臣
Set sail!
起航!
Honestly guys, I never thought I'll die like this.
夥 f我]想^我是@铀赖
I always thought I'll meet a nice girl and settle down
我以槲遇到好女孩 和她成家
and she'll eat my head.
然後她把我吃了
So sad.
真悲
We cannot give up hope.
我不能放希望
Po would want us to remain strong.
阿希望我
Hardcored! Right, Tigress?
圆豢纱! Π 悍苫?
Lord Shen, what about the bridge?
沈王 蛟觞Nk?
Nothing stands in my way.
跷艺咚
Fire!
_炮!
You coward!
你@懦夫!
Po?
阿?
How many times do I have to kill
槭颤N@死熊
the same stinking panda?
怎N⒍⒉凰腊?
Shen!
沈!
A panda stands between you and your destiny!
一b熊踝×四愕娜ヂ!
What?
啥?
Prepare yourself for a hot serving of justice.
浣邮苷x的土P吧
And bring the terror to an end.
我要Y束@隹植赖碾y
What?
啥玩意?
And now... free the Five!
F在... 我碚救w世五b!
Fist of Destruction!
缰拳!
Okay.
好吧
Take aim!
瞄!
Ready?
?
This way now...
@...
... that way...
... 那...
You can't follow me.
你打不到我
Just get him!
快把他o我值!
Come on.
受死吧
No, no, don't shoot!
e e e_火!
Don't shoot!
e_火!
Don't shoot! Shoot!
e_火! _火!
Shoot! Don't shoot!
_火! e_火!
Don't shoot! Cross fire!
e_火! 交叉射!
Attack!
攻!
Catch your freedom.
接著
Monkey!
猴王!
Impressive, Dragon Warrior.
值闷亮 神大b
What's your plan?
你有什N?
Step one, free the Five.
第一步 救出你五
What's step two?
第二步是啥?
- Honestly, I didn't think I'll make it this far.  - Po!
- 老f 我焊]想^有第二步  - 阿!
Stop Shen before he gets to the harbour.
在沈到港口之前把他截住
Guys!
夥!
Viper, puppet of death!
俏小 死亡木偶!
Tigress!
悍苫!
Master Ox!
L暴F牛大b!
Jump!
跳!
And Croc!
有流星{大b!
Vengeance is served.
我蟪鹆
- Why did you... ?  - Your friend there is very persuasive.
- 你怎N... ?  - 你的朋友可真能忽悠
Master Shifu!
傅!
Quickly! Use their boats to block the way.
快c用他的船矸怄i河道!
Crane!
`Q!
Wings of Justice!
正x之翼!
Kaka!
卡卡!
What?
怎N回事?
I... love... you... guys!
我... ... 你... !
Why aren't we firing?
槭颤N不_炮啊?
They're taking all gunmen, sir! And getting close!
他缀值袅宋所有的炮手 王! 他x我越碓浇了!
Fire then! Go fire that gun!
那不快_炮! 快_炮!
But sir! That's our own...
可是王! 那了自己人...
I said fire at them! Fire!
我f了朝他_炮! _炮!
No!
不!
Po!
阿!
Tigress?
悍苫?
As you wish,
如你所
let's finish this.
了Y了他
Fire!
_炮!
Inner peace. Inner peace. Inner peace.
刃牡钠届o 刃牡钠届o 刃牡钠届o
Again!
再!
Yeah!
耶!
Kill him! Somebody, kill him!
⒘怂! l⒘怂!
What?
什N?
No!
不要!
Keep firing! Keep firing!
^m_火啊! _火啊!
Skadoosh.
接招吧
How did you...
你是怎N...
How did you do it?
怎N做到的?
You know, you just keep your elbows up and keep the shoulders loose.
就是把肘抬高 肩膀放 你知道的
Not that. How did you find peace?
不是那些 我是f你是怎N把心o下淼?
I took away your parents. Everything.
我可是Z去了你的pH 你的一切
I scarred you for life.
我你的生活M是
See, that's the thing, Shen. Scars heal.
你看 沈 @才是PI 疤是痊K的
No, they don't. Wounds heal.
不 不 只有口才
Oh, yes. What do scars do? They fade I guess?
噢 ε 那疤呢? 它也S消失?
I don't care what scars do.
我可不P心
You should, Shen.
你P心 沈
You got to let go of that stuff from the past cause it just doesn't matter.
你忘^去 因檫^去的事根本不重要
The only thing that matters
唯一重要的
is what you choose to be now.
是你F在想要成槭颤N拥娜
You're right.
你f得
Then I choose...
那N 我x...
... this!
... @!
That was pretty hardcore.
才你可真牛
Po, come here!
阿 ^!
Don't ever do that again please.
你可千fe再那N做了
It seems you have found inner peace.
看砟憬K於找到刃牡哪欠萜届o了
At such a young age.
在如此p的年o
Well, I had a pretty good teacher.
那可不 l我有@N好的老呢
What do you mean he's not here?
你f他不在是什N意思?
It's my son's birthday.
今天可是我鹤拥纳日
All he wanted was to meet the Dragon Warrior.
他就是想要H眼神大b嘛
How about some tofu birthday cake instead, uh?
那睃c豆腐生日蛋糕怎N影?
You know, I think we'll just try again another time.
你知道N 我想我是Qrg再砗昧
When do you think he'll be back?
你J樗什Nr候回?
I don't know, okay? I don't know!
我不知道 行了吧? 我不知道!
Maybe never. I'm worried, okay.
也S永h都不回砹 我很心他好吧
But that's my job. I'm his Dad.
但那就是我的任 我是他爸爸啊
I mean, I was his dad.
我是f 我曾是他爸爸
Why did... he go and save China?
槭颤N他非得x_... 去拯救中原?
I know why. But Why?
我知道 但到底是槭颤N啊?
He's just one little panda.
他不^是只小熊而已
So, how did it go?
那 怎N影?
Did you save China?
你拯救了中原?
Yeap.
Π
Well, I knew you would.
我就知道你能行
That's why I had new signs made.
所以我早就把新招牌做好了
My son saved China. You too can save.
我鹤诱救了中原 你也可以省X啦
Buy one dumpling get one free!
子I一送一哦!
Hey, that's a pretty good deal.
嘿 @主意可真棒
Would you like to try one?
你想L一?
Maybe later.
待喊
There's something I should tell you.
有件事我得告V你
While I was gone,
在拯救中原的途中
I found a village where I was born.
我找到了我出生的那座村f
I found out how I ended up in that radish basket.
我知道我是怎NM了那b胡}N的筐子了
You did?
你都知道了?
I know who I am.
我知道我是l了
You do?
是?
I am your son.
我是你的鹤
Po.
阿
I love you, dad.
我勰 爸爸
I love you too, son.
我也勰 鹤
Delicious fat radishes.
瞧@些美味的大}N啊
You are probably hungry.
你肯定I了
Let me make you something to eat.
我o你弄c吃的去
What are you talking about? I'll cook.
你f什N呢? 我碜鲲嘛
- No, no, I'll cook.  - Dad.
- 不 不 我  - 爸
This is something I can do. You saved China.
你拯救了中原 我能槟阕龅囊簿瓦@了
No, it's the least I can do. You raised me.
不 你B育了我 相比之下我做的那都不算什N
- Po.  - Dad.
- 阿  - 爸
- Po!  - Okay.
- 阿  - 好啦
Let's both cook... together.
咱z都做... 一起做
Together.
一起
No, I'll cook.
算了 是我戆
My son is alive!
我鹤舆活著!